
{
    "krio": {
        "level1": [{
            "question": "How do you say 'Walk' ",
            "option1": "Waka",
            "option2": "Gladi",
            "option3": "Santɛm",
            "ans": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Window'",
            "option1": "Winda",
            "option2": "Pikin",
            "option3": "Os",
            "ans": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'I am going home'",
            "option1": "Nɛt",
            "option2": "A De Go Na Os",
            "option3": "Kɔmɔt na rod",
            "ans": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'I know'",
            "option1": "Lɛf",
            "option2": "A Sabi",
            "option3": "Timap",
            "ans": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'I am full'",
            "option1": "Kushɛ",
            "option2": "Tɛnki",
            "option3": "A bɛlful",
            "ans": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Stand up'",
            "option1": "Timap",
            "option2": "Man",
            "option3": "Padi kusheh-O",
            "ans": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'What?'",
            "option1": "Uman",
            "option2": "Wata",
            "option3": "Wetin",
            "ans": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Snacks'",
            "option1": "Ashɔbi",
            "option2": "Winda",
            "option3": "Mumunyɛrɛ",
            "ans": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Trousers'",
            "option1": "Tide",
            "option2": "Trɔsis",
            "option3": "Krep",
            "ans": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'What are you doing?'",
            "option1": "Ala",
            "option2": "Wetin Yu De Du",
            "option3": "Mɔt",
            "ans": 2
        }
        ],
        "level2": [{
            "age": 25,
            "position": "designer"
        },
        {
            "age": 30,
            "position": "developer"
        }]
    },
    "temne": {
        "level1": [{
            "question": "How do you say 'Hurry Up'",
            "option1": "Bʌsər",
            "option2": "Rʌ Fɔy",
            "option3": "KeKe",
            "ans": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Peanut'",
            "option1": "Mɔt",
            "option2": "Mʌ Kʌntər",
            "option3": "Ro Kaŋ",
            "ans": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Provinces'",
            "option1": "Ro Gbaŋ",
            "option2": "Po",
            "option3": "Beki",
            "ans": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Sit Down'",
            "option1": "Kʌ Tis",
            "option2": "Yirʌ",
            "option3": "Kʌ Bo",
            "ans": 2
        },
        {
           "question": "How do you say 'I’ll be back '",
            "option1": "Kʌ Swit",
            "option2": "Sɛkɛ",
            "option3": "I Tə Kʌl Der",
            "ans": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'I am going home'",
            "option1": "I Kɔnɛ Ro Seth",
            "option2": "Man",
            "option3": "Kʌ Gbara",
            "ans": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Mouth'",
            "option1": "Uman",
            "option2": "Kʌ Səŋ",
            "option3": "Wath Bɛra",
            "ans": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'I am on my way'",
            "option1": "Ashɔbi",
            "option2": "Mari",
            "option3": "I yi rə roŋ",
            "ans": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Onions'",
            "option1": "Kʌ Fənt",
            "option2": "Kʌ Yaba",
            "option3": "Krep",
            "ans": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Tomorrow'",
            "option1": "Ninʌŋ",
            "option2": "Wath runi",
            "option3": "Yathri",
            "ans": 1
        }
        ],
        "level2": [{
            "age": 25,
            "position": "designer"
        },
        {
            "age": 30,
            "position": "developer"
        }]
    }
}